



Ali Kilic

Nationality: Turkish

(+90) 5534259487

Date of birth: 23 Sep 1989

Gender: Male

☑ Email address: ali.kilic@gislayer.com

Website: https://www.alikilic.org/

Website: https://gislayer.com/

○ Whatsapp Messenger : +905534259487

▼ Twitter: https://twitter.com/alikilic harita

Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/alikilicinst

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alikilicharita/

► YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHZnHRWYfFomnAEHGP0egZw

GitHUB:: https://github.com/gislayer

• Address: Ugur Mumcu Mahallesi Menemen, 35660 Izmir (Turkey)

ABOUT ME

I was 14 when I wrote my first code. The most sacred feeling; I still love to write code. While studying Geomatic Engineering, I got acquainted with GIS technologies and These were all desktop software. Web technologies always excite me. Then I wanted to combine GIS and Web technologies. I realized my strength when I produced Web GIS software that is as powerful as desktop programs. I have produced GIS software for many companies, professors and public sector. I like to succeed and keep fighting until I achieve success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Founder of GISLayer

gislayer.com [1 Jan 2019 - Current]

City: Izmir

Country: Turkey

Manager and Developer. The codebase was developed by Ali Kilic

Editor: https://editor.gislayer.com Mobile: https://mobile.gislayer.com Other Information: https://gislayer.com

Freelance - Sr. GIS Developer

Techmaven Geospatial [1 Jun 2018 - Current]

City: Florida

Country: United States

- Web GIS Developer
- API Manager
- Openlayers, Leaflet and Mopbox Developer

GIS Engineer

Cairn Advisors [25 Feb 2021 - Current]

City: Atlanta, Georgia, Country: United States

- Subsea Cable Collecting from Map
- OPGW Cables Managing
- Fibre Cable Mapping
- Network Anaysis
- Data Managing

Freelance - Sr. GIS Developer

Infrapedia [13 May 2018 - 1 Oct 2020]

City: San Francisco
Country: United States

- Geoserver Manager
- Mapbox Developer
- Postgis PostgreSQL Manager
- Web GIS Developer

Sr. GIS Developer

Baskent NaturalGAS Dist. INC [11 Dec 2017 - 31 Mar 2020]

City: Ankara Country: Turkey

- Web GIS Developer
- SAP GIS Integration
- Network Analyzer
- Oracle Spatial Db Managing
- Android GIS APP Developer
- NodeJS Developer
- Openlayers and TurfJS developer
- Geoserver Manager

Ir. GIS Developer

Konya Metropolitan Municipality [16 Mar 2015 – 20 Jun 2017]

City: Konya
Country: Turkey

- Web GIS Developer
- Oracle Spatial Query Building
- C# Developer
- Geoserver & Leaflet JS Developer

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Geomatics & Software Engineering

Selcuk University [8 Oct 2008 - 7 Jun 2015]

Address: Konya (Turkey)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Front-End Skills

Web GIS / HTML/CSS/JS/NodeJS / Websocket / OpenLayers / MapBox / Leaflet js / CSS / HTML / JavaScript / Git / Object-Oriented Programming / Bootstrap / JSON / XML

Back-End Skills

Nodejs - Backend / Python / API / PHP Language / SOAP / .Net Web Services / c# / RestFul API / Linux / RESTful api

Database Skills

Oracle SQL & Oracle spatial / SQL / NoSQL (MongoDB) / MySQL / PostGIS / PostgreSQL

GIS Skills

GeoServer / Remote Signing / QGIS / Mapbox-gl / ArcGIS / CesiumJS / Spatial Analyst / Openlayers / QGIS - Quantum GIS / Pitney Bowes MapInfo / Arcpy and Python / ArcGis 10.8 / ArcGIS Javascript API / LeafletJS / Photogr ametry / Spatial Queries / Geographical Information Systems (GIS) / GISLayer

Mobile Skills

Mobile application development: Android, Flutter / Flutter Dart / Flutter Framework

PROIECTS

GISLayer and Other Projects

[1 Jan 2014 – 1 Jan 2021]

This is my projects page: https://www.alikilic.org/projects

This is my Local Tile Server: https://gislayer.com/local-tile-server

With GISLayer you will have learned all my skills.

- 1. I can manage spatial files on a WebGIS: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/2-add-vector-layer-files/
- 2. Layer Management: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/3-using-layerbox/
- 3. **OGC Services Usage**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/4-adding-wfs-service/
- 4. **Vector Tile Usage**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/7-adding-pbf-and-mvt-vector-tile-service/
- 5. **Drawing and Editing Skills**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/11-vector-drawing-on-the-map/
- 6. Measurement Skills: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/13-measuring-length-and-area-on-the-map/
- 7. **Feature Information Managing**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/14-getting-information-from-vector-feature-on-the-map/
- 8. Changing Feature Style: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/23-changing-feature-color-in-attribute-table/
- 9. **OSM Skills**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/26-downloading-open-street-map-osm-vector-data-from-the-map/
- 10. Spatial Skills: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/28-creating-buffers-around-geometries/
- 11. Raster Skills: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/39-view-geotiff/
- 12. Managing Cloud Based Projects: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/45-saving-and-displaying-system-files/
- 13. **Team Works Managing**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/47-sharing-system-file/
- 14. Public Map Sharing: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/48-displaying-files-and-people-you-share/
- 15. Remote Sensing Skills: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/60-remote-sensing-analysis/
- 16. **Heatmap Anaylisis**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/66-heatmap-density-map-analysis/
- 17. Thematic Map Analysis: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/67-thematic-map-analysis/
- 18. **Evelation Data Managing**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/75-creating-elevation-profile/
- 19. **POI Data Managing**: https://gislayer.com/docs/editor/74-google-poi-data-collecting/

and many skill you can find on here: https://gislayer.com/gislayer-web-gis-software-usage

Which technology i used on this project: https://gislayer.com/web-based-gis-project-software

https://www.alikilic.org/projects

https://gislayer.com/web-based-gis-project-software

https://gislayer.com/gislayer-web-gis-software-usage

https://gislaver.com/bluegis-mobile-gis-software

https://gislayer.com/bluegis-mobile-gis-software-usage

https://www.alikilic.org/blog